

ADDRESS

Obafemi Awolowo University Oloyede Estate, Modakeke Ile Ife 220254

CONTACT

- **L** +2348063736400
- https://victorblessed.me
- victorheywhy@gmail.com
- **3 18 March 1994**
- **y** victor_heywhy
- victorheywhy
- in victorheywhy

CERTIFICATIONS

The Ultimate SEO

Training 2021 + SEO For **Wordpress Websites**

Joshua George (Udemy)

The Ultimate Copywriting Course -

Write Copy that Sells 2021

Joshua Geoge (Udemy)

The Ultimate Digital **Marketing Course**

Joshua Geoge (Udemy)

The Ultimate Google **Analytics Course**

Joshua Geoarge (Udemy)

LANGUAGES

English Very Fluent **Yoruba** Conversational

REFERENCES

Samuel Ajibade

Real Estate Analyst. (Everyday Luxury Inc.) +2348038465564

samuel@everydaylux.com

Perfection Loveday

CEO of Veehue Labs +234 807 071 8502 lovedayperfection1@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Writing

Web Surfing

Studying

Music

Gaming

Movies

Sporting

ABOUT & OBJECTIVES

I'm a professional content writer and video ads creator. With over 5 years' experience. I have been able to work with several companies and individual YouTubers in various niches: helping them convert audiences into subscribers through my portfolio over time.

From descriptive to analytical and scripts that take on a story-telling style, I have just what it takes to draw your audiences' interest and gear it towards any direction you want.

I also have an objective to work with a team of talented professionals, who, by virtue, have a strong believe in work problem solving mindset of using dedication, team work and creativity, to achieve corporate mission and vision, thereby adding value and leaving an enduring legacy for future generation.

KEY SKILLS

Commercial Video Ads Scriptwriting

YouTube Ads **Freelance**

Whitepaper Creation Digital Marketing

Search Engine Optimization Affiliate Marketing

(SEO)

Storyboards Filmmaking

Data Entry Social Media Management

WORK EXPERIENCE

Adeyemi College of Education

(March 2018 - April 2020)

July 2021

August

2021

July

2021

May

2021

Contributed to the development of the Department of English by writing great educational content.

Pak Filmmakers Scriptwriter

Official scriptwriter for PakFilmmakers, and we have excellent

(April 2019 - Present)

- reviews from thousands of clients all over the world. We help take businesses and companies to the greatest level by
- making stunning commercial video advertisements.

Fiverr Freelance Writer

(March 2016 - Present)

- I manage different writing projects for different buyers on Fiverr Platform without compromising on the success of any.
- I make custom changes by modifying scripts and blog posts to suit clients' requirements.
- I always ensure that each business stands out great by creating amazing video scripts, content, and video ads that rhymes with each business' identity.
- I handle the creation of e-commerce stores for businesses using platforms like Shopify and Wordpress.

Fiverr

E-commerce Developer

(August 2019 - Present)

- Handled the creation of e-commerce stores for businesses using platforms like Shopify and WordPress. Managed different projects at a time without compromising on the
- perfection of any. Made custom changes by modifying the source code of both
- Shopify and WordPress to suit clients' requirements.

Fiverr

Key Achievements

(July 2016 - Present)

- Crafted out several writeups in categories including web content, articles, scripts, blogs, and much more.
- Got ranked as a Level 2 seller on Fiverr, the greater of which is the Top-Rated Seller.

Veehue Labs, NG Research Expert

Worked on Veehue Labs, together with a few friends as, as a

(August 2021 - Present)

- business accelerator startup geared towards helping businesses grow. Joined the Pioneer to recommend and consult clients on making
- decisions about the most appropriate solution for their business.
- Assisted the team in creating content while ensuring an effective and fun workflow.

DOW7 Coin White Paper Developer & Designer

(August 2021 - Present)

Worked with the company to draft out their detailed and well-

designed white paper that portray, to the world, the benefits of their project and how it can help transform lives.

EDUCATION Obafemi Awolowo University (Adeyemi

Chapter) Bachelor's Degree English Language 2020) 3.5

(January 2017 - April

Studied English Language in the Faculty of Education, with the focus

(December 2007 -

December 2010)

2015)

3.5

of working with a team of talented professionals, who by virtue have a strong believe in work problem solving mindset of using dedication, team work and creativity in English. (January 2012 - November Adeyemi College of Education, Ondo

Language

Nigeria Certificate in Education, (NCE) English

Senior Secondary School Certificate (SSCE) Senior

Secondary School Certificate (SSCE

Osogbo Grammar School, Osogbo

Completed every necessary requirement for the O'level degree certificate in accordance with WAEC's (West African Examination Council) requirements. Studied courses included Mathematics, English, Literature-in-English...

PERSONAL QUALIFICATION & SKILL

Excellent Oral and Written Communication Skills